gulfjobseeker.com 2010-11-23

# Privacy Policy

|    
---  
  
Gulfjobseeker.com is a venture of First Impression Management Consultancy, Dubai, UAE. We are committed to protect privacy of our registered job seekers, employers or recruiters and do not tolerate spam and will never sell, rent, lease or give away your information (name, address, email, etc.) to any third party unknown to us nor will we send you unsolicited emails.   

If you choose to give your name and email address into one or more of our site's registration forms, then we will send you emails relating to the mailing list(s) or service(s) you joined and the newsletter, as well as marketing offers from time to time. You may opt out of receiving future mailings from our mailing lists by clicking on unsubscribe link or replying to back to email address with Remove or Unsubscribe in subject. You stop receiving such emails in 7 working days of your request for unsubscribe.  

Our goal is to provide you with a secure online experience and to ensure that any information you submit to us is private and used/disclosed only for the purposes and in the means described below.   

As a human resource consultancy our website gulfjobseeker.com ask job seekers and employers to submit information relevant to the job / candidate search in order to conduct / optimize / facilitate the job search functionality or related career support services. All the information is submitted exclusively on a voluntary basis. Please note that we are not a Recruitment Agency and provide Free Registration to Employers and Job Seekers.  

Please find below details of our member privacy practices.  

**Registration**  

To fully participate in career support services, candidate databases or search activities, we require you to register in Gulfjobseeker.com. Non-registered users are granted partial participation access e.g. non-registered job seekers may view positions posted but cannot apply until they have not completed registration process.   

To register, we will ask for contact plus resume information (job seekers and employers) and information on your company (employers). Gulfjobseeker.com is the sole owner of information collected through registration pages and we will not disclose this information to anyone outside of our organisation or partner sites (www.fundadvisor.in, www.datachampion.com, www.indiajobexpert.com) Your contact information (such as name and e-mail address may however be used to contact you about any features/services/job alerts/support/career related.  

services offered on our sites, which we believe may be of interest to registered users with unsubscribe link in each message. Our goal is to provide our users with a personalized experience every time they log onto Gulfjobseeker.com and to that end we may direct you to jobs/articles/forums/resource/partner website links etc. that we think assist you in your career / lifestyle activities.  

**CV Registration**  

CV's can be added to our database and can be removed by deactivating your registration. We do not delete CV's or contact information from our database, due to record keeping purpose such as user activity logs, payment information and management comments, but instead DEACTIVATE the file. This means that while your CV is 'parked' at Gulfjobseeker.com for your access and reference at any point in time, no employers or other members will have access to view or search it through our search functionality.   

CVs with registration can be reactivated once again by requesting to [_support@gulfjobseeker.com_](mailto:support@gulfjobseeker.com) to make your file ACTIVE again. This would enable any employer members who have paid to register with our service to access your CV. We are not responsible for the privacy of any copies of your CV or your contact information that are subsequently retained by employer members in their own private files and databases.   

As an additional privacy function, job seekers have the option to block the name of their current employer from any CV been distributed by e-mail in employer database.   

You may edit/change information on your CV at any point in time. You may also remove / deactivate your CVs from our databases at any point in time.  

**Job Postings**  

Employers are asked to submit detailed contact information and information about the position requirements as part of their job posting activity. Information is submitted purely voluntarily or by our staff members. Job details may be viewed by any registered job seeker or site visitor. Non-registered site visitors may view position but cannot apply until they have registered their details. As an additional privacy feature, employers may hide their company name when their jobs are viewed online. Your privacy will thus be assured while job seekers have the option to reply to the job posting.  

You may change/modify/delete any information you provide at any point in time.  

**Your Account Space**  

Registered job seekers and employers have access to a personal workspace from where they can manage/document their job/candidate search history/ mark jobs/ mark CV confidential. All information in this space can only be viewed by the registered user(s) and accessed after logging in with your password.  

Use of Cookies and Other Technologies  
   
Gulfjobseeker.com Getty uses “cookie” to enable you to sign in to our services and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard drive. Cookies contain information, including personal information, that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. The information that cookies collect includes the date and time of your visit, your registration information, and your navigational and purchase history.   

Cookies offer you many conveniences. They allow us to identify registered users when they return to the site so that they can retrieve previous login date, time and user information. Cookies also save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information.  

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of our sites and services that depend on cookies.  

In addition to cookies, we may use other technologies, including single-pixel gifs (also known as web beacons) on our websites and in our e-mail messages or newsletters. These tiny electronic images assist us in determining how many users have visited certain pages or opened messages or newsletters. We do not use these images to collect personal information.   

**Email Referrals**  

If you choose to use our email referral services to tell a friend about our products or services, job postings, etc., we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will use that information to send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site and review the product or service you have selected. This data is not stored in our database at all.   

**Children**  

We do not intend to solicit or collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are under 18, you should not use or enter information on this site, including without limitation, any Interactive Areas of the site.   

**Links-Widgets-Employer-Recruiter Websites**  
   
We may link to websites, including those of our third-party content providers, that have different privacy policies and practices from those disclosed here. We assume no responsibility for the policies or practices of such linked sites, and encourage you to become acquainted with them prior to use.   

**Financial Information**  

No information on credit card number and expiration date is collected by our sites and we have outsourced these payment authorisation activities to our secured banking partners Mashreq Bank and 2checkout.com Kindly read through their privacy policy before use on their respective websites.  

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  

Gulfjobseeker.com and its owner First Impression Management Consultancy will continue to commit itself on protecting and maximizing users' privacy, but holds right to change without prior notice. This Privacy Policy came into effect in 2004 and was last updated on 15th July 2009. Any updates to this policy will be published on this page.  

Contacting Us  

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of the Gulfjobseeker.com web site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us on [_anup@gulfjobseeker.com_](mailto:anup@gulfjobseeker.com) or phone us on +9714-3970978 Ext 507.
